Contact

2052530321 (Mobile) dsjones88@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-jones-74a241114 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Clinical Education
Nursing
Leadership

Honors-Awards

Most Friendly
President's List
Dean's List
Outstanding Male Nurse

Daniel Jones

Travel Nurse Cardiac Cath Lab/Electrophysiology Lab Trussville, Alabama

Summary

I have worked in the medical field in different capacities for over 7 years. I love to travel and explore new cities. I enjoy what I do, whether it be taking care of patients, or educating medical personnel on how to use equipment and devices. I know that God has a plan for me. I will not stop to achieve my dreams.

Experience

UAB Medicine Cardiac Catheterization Laboratory Nurse August 2018 - Present (2 years)

BayCare Health System
Travel Nurse
January 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months)
United States

Baptist Memorial Health Care 3 years

Travel Nurse

August 2017 - Present (3 years)

Travel Nurse August 2017 - December 2017 (5 months)

HCA

Travel Registered Nurse
May 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Johns Hopkins Hospital Travel Registered Nurse December 2016 - May 2017 (6 months)

Baltimore, Maryland Area

The Medical Affairs Company Clinical Nurse Educator May 2016 - November 2016 (7 months) AL/GA

Building relationships, teaching, and impacting medical professionals

B. Braun Medical
Clinical Education Specialist
October 2015 - April 2016 (7 months)

I travel all over the country and continent to educate and engage nurses and medical staff about products that are new to their hospital.

I personally go around to every unit in the hospital and teach staff about products that are about to begin using.

I instruct the staff on what makes our products great and how to properly use products.

I also instruct in the classroom, pending on what line of products are being introduced to that particular hospital.

Cross Country TravCorps
Travel RN
April 2015 - October 2015 (7 months)
Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area; Charleston, SC

Worked at Tampa General in the MICU; also worked in the CVICU at MUSC in Charleston.

Took care of patients with L and R vads, bi-vads, abiomeds, as well as general surgical patients.

The University of Alabama at Birmingham Critical Care RN February 2012 - April 2015 (3 years 3 months)

Worked in Heart and Lung Transplant Intensive Care unit for 2 years. I took care of pre and post-op patients for heart and lung transplantations. Also worked with L-Vad patients, R- Vad patients, Bi-Vad, and balloon pump patients, as well destination therapy or a bridge to transplant.

I worked for 15 months on the medical/surgical floor. I took care of a wide variety of patients while providing excellent care. Learned excellent time management

Pine Tree Country Club Waiter/Bartender/Banquet Server May 2009 - January 2011 (1 year 9 months)

I was a server/waiter at the country club. I worked parties including: banquets, wedding receptions, weddings, birthday parties, etc.

Education

University of Alabama at Birmingham
Bachelor's Degree, Science in Nursing · (2007 - 2011)

University of Alabama at Birmingham